MakeMKV v1.18.3 win(x86-release) started
You are running a 32-bit (x86) version of a program. Eventually this will be deprecated in upcoming versions, please upgrade to a processor manufactured during last 10 years...
Using direct disc access mode
Title #1 was added (56 cell(s), 2:58:57)
Operation successfully completed
Saving 1 titles into directory file://C:\Users\dusti\Videos\The Lord of the Rings- The Two Towers (2002)
1 titles saved
Copy complete. 1 titles saved.
